http://www.suncoastrv.com/privacy-policy/

Updated: December 31, 2019
We are committed to protecting the privacy of personal information and the responsible use of that information to deliver personalized, relevant content to our customers. This Privacy Policy applies to this website or mobile application and the websites and mobile applications that display this Privacy Policy (collectively, Sites). We may also operate additional websites or mobile applications that are governed by their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures for the collection, use and disclosure of your information and data on these Sites and the services available through them (Services).
Our Sites also contain a link to our Terms of Use which govern your use of these Sites and the Services available through them. You understand that by using these Sites or Services you agree to the terms of both this Privacy Policy and the Website Terms of Use.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT
The personally identifiable information we collect may include your name, address, zip code, phone number, email address, and other identifying information, and may also include information about vehicles you own or lease, such as sales and service transaction history, vehicle payments, VIN, and mileage (collectively, Personal Information or PI). We collect PI in a number of different ways and from a number of different sources. We collect PI you provide us through our Sites or when using certain aspects of our Services. We may also collect PI you provide to manufacturers, our authorized vendors, or affiliates, as well as information we obtain from third party databases (collectively, our Partners).
As part of our Services, we may communicate with you via email, call, chat or text. In this capacity, we would have the ability and authorization to read or listen and retain the content of those communications, including contact information. In all cases, the information we may retain and how we may use it are subject to this Privacy Policy and applicable law.
We may also collect usage information about how our Sites and Services are accessed and used. This may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type, type of device used, pages on our Sites that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
We use your PI to provide information you request about our products or services, to respond to your inquiries, and to customize information and advertising that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use your PI to provide you with marketing materials, as well as other information we believe may be relevant to you. We also use remarketing services to advertise to you on third party websites, such as Google, Bing, YouTube and Facebook and their partners. To control or opt out of any of their ad services, or to review their privacy policies, please visit their sites.
We may also use your PI by combining it with non-personal information and aggregating it with information collected from others. We use this aggregated data in a number of ways, such as to improve the quality and value of our Services and to analyze and understand how our Services are used. In addition, we may provide aggregated data to our Partners so that they may understand how people use our Services or their own.
Your PI may be shared with our Partners, and may also be disclosed to third parties who work with us or our Partners. Vehicle manufacturers, for example, may use that information to contact you. We may also work with third parties that provide certain functions or services on our behalf, such as marketing, communications, analyzing data or authenticating contact information.
We require our third party service providers to contractually commit to protecting your PI in accordance with both industry standards and applicable law. While we have implemented policies and procedures to protect PI, we cannot control, and are not responsible for, the manner in which our Partners or other third parties use that PI. Accordingly, you should review their privacy policies, as well.
EXTERNAL LINKS
Our Sites or Services may contain links to other third-party websites. After you leave our Sites, we have no control over the information collected from or about you. We are not responsible, and assume no liability, for the privacy policies and/or practices on any third-party websites. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected by us on our Sites.
COOKIES, ETC
We use a number of technologies to automatically collect information, including cookies, tracking pixels and web beacons. “Cookies” are small text files sent from a web server that are stored on your device and enable a site to remember you or your preferences. We may use cookies to recognize you and optimize your experiences when visiting our Sites and using our Services. Tracking pixels are small images utilized to track a user, typically for advertising or analytics purposes. Web beacons allow data to be exchanged between systems. Our Sites may also be monitored by one or more third-party monitoring software(s), and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our Services. We may use one or more of these technologies on our Sites to transmit information to you or about you and connect information about you from different sources, websites, devices, and mobile applications. For data being collected through one of these technologies, Compass Capture , you may opt-out by clicking here: Unsubscribe.
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Sites or Services. Some browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” (DNT) feature that, when turned on, signals to websites and online services that you do not want to be tracked. However, as there is no accepted standard for how to respond to DNT signals, we do not currently support DNT signals, other than cookies.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR DATA
We use safeguards that satisfy generally accepted industry standards to preserve the integrity and security of your PI. However, we cannot guarantee the security of information you provide us with certainty or warrant it will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons. We will make all legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your PI, in the manner and within the time periods required by applicable law.
JURISDICTIONS
Your PI is collected and used by us within the United States. We make no representation that our Privacy Policy complies with the laws of any foreign jurisdictions, including the European Union’s General Data Privacy Regulation. If you choose to provide us with PI from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with any applicable foreign laws.
COMPLIANCE WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT
We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials, as well as private parties, to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process, including, but not limited to, subpoenas, to protect our property and rights or that of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or subject to legal action.
OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN
Our Sites and Services are not targeted to or intended for use by children. We are concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the internet. Accordingly, we will not knowingly request PI online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior, verifiable parental consent. Unfortunately, we cannot always determine the age of a visitor to our Sites or user of our Services.
CORPORATE TRANSFERS
In connection with a corporate merger, acquisition, divestiture, asset sale, joint venture, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or any other similar transaction or proceeding, we may sell, divest, transfer, assign, share or otherwise engage in a transaction that involves some or all of our assets, including your PI.
OPTING OUT
If you wish to stop receiving email communications from us, you may “unsubscribe” using the link at the bottom of the email you receive. If you wish to be placed on our postal mailing Do Not Contact list, see the “How to Contact Us” section below and provide the name and address as listed on the mailing. To stop text communications, respond to the text with the words “STOP”. You may also control ads appearing on your browser or mobile device by adjusting your settings or using third party ad blocking tools.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you are a California resident, the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides you with certain rights concerning your personal information, including the right to know how and for what purpose businesses collect it, the right to access your data, the right to opt-out of it being sold to third parties and, subject to certain exclusions for legitimate business purposes, the right to have it deleted. If you have further inquiries about your information under the CCPA or wish to opt-out, please contact us as specified below under How to Contact Us.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
We may modify our Privacy Policy, at any time and for any reason, by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Site. Your use of our Sites or Services after any such posting indicates your acceptance of our modified Privacy Policy.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy when using our Sites or Services, or wish to exercise your rights under the CCPA, please click here to email us: Contact Us. California residents may also call us tollfree at 1-800-624-7094 . In certain circumstances, you may have the right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. We will make every effort to respond promptly and address your concerns.
LOCATIONS
Jacksonville, Fl
(904) 297-1736
9070 Beach Blvd Jacksonville, FL 32216
Brooksville, Fl
(352) 557-9120
15265 Cortez Blvd, Brooksville, FL 34613
Ocala, Fl
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
About: Travelcamp is the Southeast Premier RV dealer with five locations throughout Florida and Georgia.
Contact Us: We want to hear it! Let us know how your experience was, good or bad, and someone will contact you back in 48 business hours or less!
We strive to ensure all pricing and information contained in this website is accurate. Despite our efforts, occasionally errors resulting from typos, inaccurate detail information or technical mistakes may occur. We are not responsible for any such errors and reserve the right to correct them at any time.
Search
